Pam Bondi said it's on her desk Right next to truth and civil unrest One day it's there, the next Group finished like ethics in a voting booth Promises made from the podium high Now they gaslight with a straight-up lie Said we'll drain the swamp, yeah sure you did Just made a list and buried it with the kids, the list That doesn't exist, kids burn While they shake their fists, the list
That never saw light Buried deep in a billionaire's flight They shrink, bake, use and twist the plot But the names on the list sure remember a lot It's the list, shh, the list, shh The list that doesn't exist
Reporter as they start to sweat, to the yelling and the press reset.
That's fake, that's false, that's Soros trash.
How justice drowns in private jets and cash.
Their fingers all smell like kerosene, while they gas up the memory machine.
Rewrite the script with a Sharpie pen, while Epstein's ghost just laughs again.
A list that doesn't exist got filed, with the other drifts the list.
That slipped through the cracks, now sits on a yacht with knives in bay!
Hoaxin' witch hunts, same old spin, while victims wait for truth to begin.
It's the list.
The list.
The list that doesn't exist!
Sir, do you know who's on the list?
I don't know, I've never seen a list.
There may be a list.
It might not be real.
What even is a list?
Is it even legal?
FLASH MOVE POP THE CROWD GOES NUMB ANOTHER SCANDAL HERE IT COMES BUT DON'T YOU DARE TRY TO INSIST THAT THERE'S ANYTHING REAL ON THAT DAMN LIST
The list that doesn't exist Stay sealed with the pervert's kiss The list that we'll never see Because the truth ain't made in D.C.
Oh, scream it loud, don't let them win They hid the list in all their sins It's the list, the list, the list that doesn't exist